{
    "subject": "resource/On_the_Black_Hill_(film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Film",
    "human_readable": "On the Black Hill is a type of Film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8520689606666565,
            "question": "Is 'On the Black Hill' a documentary?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6535273790359497,
            "question": "Who directed 'On the Black Hill'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.633334219455719,
            "question": "What genre is 'On the Black Hill'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6017193794250488,
            "question": "Where was 'On the Black Hill' filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5347216129302979,
            "question": "Can you describe the plot of 'On the Black Hill'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5200566053390503,
            "question": "What actors are in 'On the Black Hill'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49664145708084106,
            "question": "What kind of story does 'On the Black Hill' tell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3837369680404663,
            "question": "What is the main theme of 'On the Black Hill'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23244254291057587,
            "question": "When was 'On the Black Hill' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1487775593996048,
            "question": "Has 'On the Black Hill' won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=On the Black Hill is a type of Film.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5961_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was 'On the Black Hill' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5961_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the main theme of 'On the Black Hill'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5961_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of story does 'On the Black Hill' tell?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5961_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5961_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5961_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5961_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5961_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5961_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5961_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5961_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5961_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5961_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5961_71.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly indicate that \"On the Black Hill\" is indeed a film, supporting the statement that it is a type of Film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}